Guide to the Acacia Fraternity records,1906-2007.
Acacia Fraternity records
- Series XIV. Ledgers
  - Treasurer Ledgers, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Series XV. Masonic Literature, 1923-2005; Various printed materials related to the New York Council of Deliberation, Ancient Accepted Scottish Rite Northern Masonic Jurisdiction. These materials were collected by members of the Cornell Chapter of Acacia Fraternity during the years of its formal affiliation with Masonry, 1907 to 1933. These materials survived the various moves of the chapter and were stored in the chapter library. In February 2012, as part of a complete renovation of the library, the decision was made by Thomas Balcerski and Steve Stein to relocate these materials to the Acacia Fraternity Records held by the Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections. It is hoped these materials will be of interest to researchers of Masonic history and especially the history of Masons in New York State.
  - 1908 Proceedings of the Council of Deliberation, State of New York, Ancient Accepted Scottish Rite Northern Masonic Jurisdiction. Buffalo, New York., July 25, 1908 (Box 20)
  - 1910 Proceedings of the Council of Deliberation, State of New York, Ancient Accepted Scottish Rite Northern Masonic Jurisdiction. Corning, New York., July 27, 1910 (Box 20)
  - 1911 Proceedings of the Council of Deliberation, State of New York, Ancient Accepted Scottish Rite Northern Masonic Jurisdiction. Rochester, New York., June 26, 1911 (Box 20)
  - 1912 Proceedings of the Council of Deliberation, State of New York, Ancient Accepted Scottish Rite Northern Masonic Jurisdiction. Niagara Falls, New York., July 1, 1912 (Box 20)
  - 1915 Proceedings of the Council of Deliberation, State of New York, Ancient Accepted Scottish Rite Northern Masonic Jurisdiction. Brooklyn, New York., September 10, 1915 (Box 20)
  - 1916 Proceedings of the Council of Deliberation, State of New York, Ancient Accepted Scottish Rite Northern Masonic Jurisdiction. Olean, New York., October 28, 1916 (Box 20)
  - Proceedings of the Council of Deliberation, State of New York, Ancient Accepted Scottish Rite Northern Masonic Jurisdiction. Syracuse, New York. October 29, 1917. With Supplement by G. Alfred Lawrence, 32o, M.D., Ph.D., Formerly Grand Surgeon, N.Y. Council of Deliberation. List of Officers of the Bodies of the Ancient Accepted Scottish Rite in the State of New York, 1867—1917. (Box 20)
  - Proceedings of the Fifty-Eighth Council of Deliberation, State of New York, Ancient Accepted Scottish Rite Northern Masonic Jurisdiction. Utica, New York. Saturday, July 30, 1927. With Supplement by G. Alfred Lawrence, 32o, M.D., Ph.D., Formerly Grand Surgeon, N.Y. Council of Deliberation. List of Officers of the Bodies of the Ancient Accepted Scottish Rite in the State of New York, 1867—1927. (Box 20)
  - Proceedings of the Grand Lodge of Free and Accepted Masons of the State of New York. One hundred and fiftieth annual communication., May 1931 (Box 20)
  - List of Members of the Supreme Council of Sovereign Grand Inspectors-General of the Thirty-Third and Last Degree, Ancient Accepted Scottish Rite for the Northern Masonic Jurisdiction of the United States of America; Officers of the Council of Deliberation and Officers of the Various Subordinate Scottish Rite Bodies of the State of New York to December 31, 1917, by G. Alfred Lawrence, 32o, M.D., Ph.D., Formerly Grand Surgeon, N.Y. Council of Deliberation. (Box 20)
  - List of Members of the Supreme Council of Sovereign Grand Inspectors-General of the Thirty-Third and Last Degree, Ancient Accepted Scottish Rite for the Northern Masonic Jurisdiction of the United States of America; Officers of the Council of Deliberation and Officers of the Various Subordinate Scottish Rite Bodies of the State of New York to December 31, 1927, by G. Alfred Lawrence, 32o, M.D., Ph.D., Formerly Grand Surgeon, N.Y. Council of Deliberation. (Box 20)
  - Proceedings of the Supreme Council of Sovereign Grand Inspectors-General of the Thirty-Third and Last Degree, Ancient Accepted Scottish Rite for the Northern Masonic Jurisdiction of the United States of America from March 21, 1847, to May 20, 1861, inclusive. Edited by G. Alfred Lawrence, o M.D., Ph.D., of New York., 1925 [Reprint] (Box 20)
  - The Masonry Glossary. International Masonry Institute, 1981 (Box 20)
  - The Master Mason. Vol. 1, 1924 (Box 20)
  - The Master Mason. Vol. 2, 1925 (Box 20)
- Series XVI. National Interfraternity Conference Minutes
  - National Interfraternity Conference Year Book, 1919 (Box 20)
  - National Interfraternity Conference Year Book, 1921 (Box 20)
  - National Interfraternity Conference Year Book, 1925 (Box 20)
  - National Interfraternity Conference Year Book, 1926 (Box 20)
  - National Interfraternity Conference Year Book, 1927 (Box 20)
  - National Interfraternity Conference Year Book, 1929 (Box 20)
  - National Interfraternity Conference Year Book, 1932 (Box 20)
  - National Interfraternity Conference Year Book, 1935 (Box 20)
  - National Interfraternity Conference Year Book (Vol. 34), 1942 (Box 20)
  - National Interfraternity Conference Year Book (Vol. 38), 1946 (Box 20)
  - National Interfraternity Conference Year Book (Vol. 39), 1947 (Box 20)
  - National Interfraternity Conference Year Book (Vol. 41), 1949 (Box 20)
  - National Interfraternity Conference Year Book (Vol. 46), 1954 (Box 20)
  - National Interfraternity Conference Year Book (Vol. 47), 1955 (Box 20)
  - National Interfraternity Conference Year Book (Vol. 48), 1956 (Box 20)